[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2008s Iron Man, Iron Mans suit is made of iron.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the only US President to have never married?", "correct_answer": "Buchanan", "incorrect_answers": ["Cleveland", "McKinley", "Taft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word was coined by philosopher and theologian, William Whewell in 1833?", "correct_answer": "scientist", "incorrect_answers": ["holography", "magenta", "trastevere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Napoleon Dynamite, when Napoleon decides that he needs a job, where does he end up working and how much money did he get on his first day?", "correct_answer": "a chicken farm---6 dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["Foto-Hut--50 dollars", "Debs photo studio--20 dollars and a kiss", "Wendys--42 dollars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While training in Russia, Rocky Balboa was sporting a beard. Did he have a beard during his fight against Drago?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People with this disorder engage in idiosyncratic behaviors, such as wearing an odd-looking hat every day, or wearing their pants backwards.", "correct_answer": "Schizotypal Personality Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Antisocial Personality Disorder", "Narcissistic Personality Disorder", "Histrionic Personality Disorder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Pulp Fiction, how long did Butchs daddy hide the gold watch while in the POW camp?", "correct_answer": "5 years", "incorrect_answers": ["3 years", "4 years", "2 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sarah Jessica Parkers popular character Carrie Bradshaw writes a weekly column called Sex and the City for this newspaper.", "correct_answer": "The New York Star", "incorrect_answers": ["The New York Glamour", "The New York Fashionista", "The New York Observer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celebrated movie director created the character Indiana Jones, voted the second greatest movie hero by the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "George Lucas", "incorrect_answers": ["Quentin Tarantino", "Oliver Stone", "Steven Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What material is used for the making of the traditional hat from Ecuador called Panama hat?", "correct_answer": "Straw", "incorrect_answers": ["Animal skin", "Silk", "Wool"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Richard Dreyfuss has an uncredited part in The Graduate.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Babys real name in the movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Frances", "incorrect_answers": ["Jessica", "Sarah", "Penelope"]}]